<?xml version="1.0"?>
<info xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	  xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://apps.nextcloud.com/schema/apps/info.xsd">
	<id>birthday_widget</id>
	<name>Birthday Widget</name>
	<name lang="de">Geburtstags-Widget</name>
	<summary>Dashboard widget showing upcoming and recent birthdays from your contacts</summary>
	<summary lang="de">Dashboard-Widget mit bevorstehenden und vergangenen Geburtstagen aus deinen Kontakten</summary>
	<description><![CDATA[A simple dashboard widget that displays birthdays from your Nextcloud contacts. Never miss a birthday again with this elegant widget that keeps you informed about your contacts' special days.

**Features:**
- Shows birthdays grouped by Today, Upcoming, and Recent
- Displays age for each person (when birth year is available)
- Smart date formatting (Today, Tomorrow, Yesterday, weekday names)
- Highlights today's birthdays with special styling
- Automatically synced with your contacts' birthday calendar

**For Administrators:**
- Configurable date range for past and future birthdays
- Easy configuration through admin settings panel

The widget reads birthday data from the auto-generated contact_birthdays calendar, which Nextcloud creates automatically when contacts have birthday dates set.]]></description>
	<description lang="de"><![CDATA[Ein einfaches Dashboard-Widget, das Geburtstage aus deinen Nextcloud-Kontakten anzeigt. Verpasse nie wieder einen Geburtstag mit diesem eleganten Widget, das dich über die besonderen Tage deiner Kontakte informiert.

**Funktionen:**
- Zeigt Geburtstage gruppiert nach Heute, Bevorstehend und Vergangen
- Zeigt das Alter jeder Person an (wenn das Geburtsjahr verfügbar ist)
- Intelligente Datumsformatierung (Heute, Morgen, Gestern, Wochentage)
- Hebt heutige Geburtstage besonders hervor
- Automatisch synchronisiert mit deinem Kontakt-Geburtstagskalender

**Für Administratoren:**
- Konfigurierbarer Zeitraum für vergangene und zukünftige Geburtstage
- Einfache Konfiguration über die Admin-Einstellungen

Das Widget liest Geburtstagsdaten aus dem automatisch generierten contact_birthdays-Kalender, den Nextcloud automatisch erstellt, wenn Kontakte Geburtstagsdaten haben.]]></description>
	<screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/luflow/birthday-widget/refs/heads/main/appinfo/screens/screen.png</screenshot>
	<version>1.0.0</version>
	<licence>AGPL-3.0-or-later</licence>
	<author mail="florian@krautnerds.de" homepage="https://krautnerds.de">Florian Ludwig</author>
	<namespace>BirthdayWidget</namespace>
	<category>dashboard</category>
	<bugs>https://github.com/luflow/birthday-widget/issues</bugs>
	<repository type="git">https://github.com/luflow/birthday-widget</repository>
	<dependencies>
		<php min-version="8.1"/>
		<nextcloud min-version="31" max-version="32"/>
	</dependencies>
	<settings>
		<admin>OCA\BirthdayWidget\Settings\AdminSettings</admin>
		<admin-section>OCA\BirthdayWidget\Settings\AdminSection</admin-section>
	</settings>
</info>
